[Music]
me
plan specially designed for your needs
icici prove guaranteed pension plan
flexi
this plan is designed for people between
the age of 45 to 60 years and looking to
save for their retirement
the plan lets you invest small amounts
of money for a period of 15 years and
ensures a guaranteed income for life
so restart your life post retirement on
your own terms with icici guaranteed
pension plan flexi
one feature this plan offers is the
waiver of premium benefit that comes
with the joint life option
this option gives you a regular income
after retirement in case of an
unfortunate event during the premium
payment term the company will pay all
future premiums and the same income will
continue to be given to your family
member for their lifetime the icici
prove guaranteed pension plan flexi also
offers multiple benefits
regular income with regular savings
choice of 7 annuity options as per your
needs
unique options like accelerated health
boosters and booster payouts that
provide a periodic lump sum payout to
take care of your healthcare and
lifestyle needs
one percent additional annuity for
existing icici prudential life insurance
customers
save the date feature to receive your
income on the date of your choice
top-up facility to increase your income
by paying an additional premium
loan facility to get access to money
when you need it
[Music]
you